<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greg Miller - Game Designer</title>
    <link>https://gregmillerga.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Greg Miller - Game Designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gregmillerga.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bioshock and Interactive Storytelling</title>
      <link>https://gregmillerga.me/posts/bioshockarticle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregmillerga.me/posts/bioshockarticle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following segment is from a report written for a class on Interactive Narrative. The focus being to breakdown the storytelling tools the creators used to tell the award-winning story of Bioshock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bioshock was a multiplatform First-Person Shooter created by Irrational Games, which was rebranded to Ghost Story Games later on in the studio’s life. The game follows a man whose plane ends up crashing near a lighthouse, leading him to discover the underwater city of Rapture. The player must use the weapons and abilities known as Vigors to escape the madness sunk underwater. The series has a heavy focus on making an interactive world and deep world-building. The creators use multiple tools to explain and introduce the player to the world of Bioshock using multiple game writing tools. These range from direct dialogue with the player, collectible records, and environmental storytelling. All of these tools come together to deliver all the lore and dialogue in a way that feels natural, and easy for the average player to understand.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;The following segment is from a report written for a class on Interactive Narrative. The focus being to breakdown the storytelling tools the creators used to tell the award-winning story of Bioshock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bioshock was a multiplatform First-Person Shooter created by Irrational Games, which was rebranded to Ghost Story Games later on in the studio’s life. The game follows a man whose plane ends up crashing near a lighthouse, leading him to discover the underwater city of Rapture. The player must use the weapons and abilities known as Vigors to escape the madness sunk underwater. The series has a heavy focus on making an interactive world and deep world-building. The creators use multiple tools to explain and introduce the player to the world of Bioshock using multiple game writing tools. These range from direct dialogue with the player, collectible records, and environmental storytelling. All of these tools come together to deliver all the lore and dialogue in a way that feels natural, and easy for the average player to understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main vehicle for the story of Bioshock is the conversations and scenes the players have with various characters in the game world. All the characters in Bioshock are fully voice-acted, allowing for a better understanding of the characters. Throughout the game, there are three different types of scenes in the game, the first being Cutscenes. Cutscenes are entirely scripted events where control is taken away from the player. These cutscenes tend to be key moments in the game that have to happen in a specific way, as these types of scenes allow them greater control over the second to the second direction of the action. Scripted&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scenes allow the player to walk and interact with the world, but the actual actions of the scene can’t be influenced by their actions. These tend to be used when they need control over the outcome of a scene, but they can’t justify taking away control from the player. The final type of the scene is Gameplay Events, which are events that happen in reaction to the action taken by the player. These include situations such as with the Little Sisters, where you can choose to save or drain a Little Sister, which affects the ending and how it plays out when you defeat the final boss. Another example is how enemies have conversations with each other when they are unaware of the player’s location. These conversations often give a glimpse into both the minds of the current occupants, alongside the past lives they used to live in the glory of Rapture’s golden years. It also acts as a reward for players who are being careful, as the conversation will end when the player is spotted, building on the world and enforcing a gameplay style at the same time. These three types of scenes all are used to tell the main story of Bioshock, while the next two methods are used to build the background information.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://gregmillerga.me/img/BioshockReport/pic1.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Subversion Logo&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;In one of the many Scripted Scenes, a Big Daddy attacks another human from behind a glass wall. This showcases the sheer power Big Daddies have, without having to put the player in direct danger yet.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Audio Logs are used in Bioshock in order to explain key background information or tell an event that happened before the player arrived. These audio logs can be picked up by the player, and when activated they play a pre-recorded message. These logs are often framed in the game as logs of someone’s work, personal memos, or voicemails to other people. Sometimes these are messages from characters that you can encounter during an Event, and sometimes they are characters that you only hear from the various Audio Logs scattered across the game. This optional content allows the developers to not only include a lot of information without overloading the player but also allows the player to control how much content they listen to. This strikes a good balance between the people who like story-heavy video games and those that just want the raw gameplay. The final tool of Storytelling employed throughout most of Bioshock is environmental storytelling. The environments of Bioshock are filled with all sorts of details that help flesh out the backstory of Bioshock without even making the player think about it. For example, there are a lot of references to a New Years&amp;rsquo; party in 1959 throughout the city in the form of various posters and signs hanging around, despite the fact that the plane intro clearly implies the game takes place past the ’60s. In the middle of the restaurant you explore, there are still decorations from a New Years Party, and signs of an explosion going off in the middle of the dining area. This already implies something terrible happened during the party, and most likely was the downfall of their society. When the player finally discovers an audio log of a woman who died during the New Year&amp;rsquo;s attack, the player could have been able to piece together the basic scenario just by the details in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://gregmillerga.me/img/BioshockReport/pic2.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Subversion Logo&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;The scene of the New Years&#39; disaster, which led to the downfall of Rapture. Plenty of clues of what happened are buried throughout the ruins.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Bioshock is a very impressive FPS game that is able to balance having a deep and complex backstory without overwhelming casual players or players who don’t care about the story. It’s a proven model of writing content in games that other studios have started to follow in the video game industry. However, the expert-level execution of the concepts present in the game put it a cut above the rest. The way the cutscenes, audio logs, and environmental storytelling mix and enhance each other so expertly throughout the game creates an addicting storyline that’s impossible to forget about. Combined with the high interactivity of the environment and iconic art direction, it creates a living world that the player can freely explore and get immersed inside of. The game is not perfect, especially in terms of being a stable and bug-free experience, but this game’s immersion factor makes the small headaches to get this game running properly on modern Windows machines easily worth it in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrapyard Episode 1: Castle Breen</title>
      <link>https://gregmillerga.me/posts/scrapyardgame1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregmillerga.me/posts/scrapyardgame1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CASTLE BREEN (HALF-LIFE 2)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Completed on December 9th, 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created using Valve&amp;rsquo;s Hammer Editor, this two-part level was created as part of a class studying level design. Starting off stripping the player of all their weapons, the player must escape a Combine occupied Castle. This study into level design was the final project out of a series of tests, and focuses on the pacing of the experience, giving the player intense combat experiences, and a daring escape at the end. This new experience was created only using base Half-Life 2 assets and logic, used in a new context to create new types of situations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;CASTLE BREEN (HALF-LIFE 2)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Completed on December 9th, 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created using Valve&amp;rsquo;s Hammer Editor, this two-part level was created as part of a class studying level design. Starting off stripping the player of all their weapons, the player must escape a Combine occupied Castle. This study into level design was the final project out of a series of tests, and focuses on the pacing of the experience, giving the player intense combat experiences, and a daring escape at the end. This new experience was created only using base Half-Life 2 assets and logic, used in a new context to create new types of situations.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my new Site!</title>
      <link>https://gregmillerga.me/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregmillerga.me/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-my-site&#34;&gt;Welcome to my site!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is all still very much a W.I.P&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-my-site&#34;&gt;Welcome to my site!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is all still very much a W.I.P&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me!</title>
      <link>https://gregmillerga.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregmillerga.me/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;my-resume&#34;&gt;My Resume&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;2022 – Present Day&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;KingsIsle Entertainment - Associate Product Designer on Wizard101&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created content of various types using custom tools based on Gamebryo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created automation scripts using Python and C#&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Planned Roadmaps for In-Game Events and Crown Shop Rotations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Owned and led multiple mechanics in Wizard101 (Pets, Monstrology)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;2021&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Missing Link - Level Designer/Narrative Designer on Install Wizard&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designed the tutorial and other levels for the player to explore using the Unity Editor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created tools using C# to help the other level designers create content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote comedic dialogue to enhance the gameplay and story.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Led the creation of planning documents using Word and Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;my-resume&#34;&gt;My Resume&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;2022 – Present Day&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;KingsIsle Entertainment - Associate Product Designer on Wizard101&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created content of various types using custom tools based on Gamebryo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created automation scripts using Python and C#&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Planned Roadmaps for In-Game Events and Crown Shop Rotations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Owned and led multiple mechanics in Wizard101 (Pets, Monstrology)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;2021&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Missing Link - Level Designer/Narrative Designer on Install Wizard&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designed the tutorial and other levels for the player to explore using the Unity Editor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created tools using C# to help the other level designers create content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote comedic dialogue to enhance the gameplay and story.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Led the creation of planning documents using Word and Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;2020&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Man Down Studios - Lead Designer on Blackout&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submitted game as part of the Ubisoft Game Lab Competition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prototyped puzzles and gameplay in the Unreal Engine Editor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created and adjusted Blueprints to add functionality to the game.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Led testing on the game and helped release it on itch.io for free (&lt;a href=&#34;https://ameliarose.itch.io/blackout%29&#34;&gt;https://ameliarose.itch.io/blackout)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborated with our composer to create a soundtrack that reacts to the player’s progression.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote and drew various design documents using Word, Powerpoint, and Photoshop.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;technical-tools&#34;&gt;Technical Tools:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Coding&lt;/th&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Version Control&lt;/th&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Art Tools&lt;/th&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Planning&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/devicons/devicon@latest/icons/csharp/csharp-plain.svg&#34;  alt=&#34;C# Logo&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;C# for Unity and Standalone Applications&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/devicons/devicon@latest/icons/subversion/subversion-original.svg&#34;  alt=&#34;Subversion Logo&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;Subversion for Version Control&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;A3&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Ap(1-3)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/devicons/devicon@latest/icons/python/python-plain.svg&#34;  alt=&#34;Python Logo&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;Python for Automation and Tools&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/devicons/devicon@latest/icons/git/git-original.svg&#34;  alt=&#34;Python Logo&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;Git for Version Control&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;A6&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Ap(4-6)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;B1&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;B2&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;B3&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Bp(1-3)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;B4&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;B5&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;B6&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Bp(4-6)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jetbrain IDEs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual Studio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;testimonial&#34;&gt;Testimonial&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I worked with Greg in the Ubisoft game lab competition on Blackout. He is one of the best designers I know and an all around great guy. Greg consistently took on extra responsibilities such as level implementation, bug fixing and testing. He was always ready with a helping hand and a sense of humor.&amp;rdquo; &lt;code&gt;Amelia Payne - Man Down Studio, Microsoft &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Greg and I collaborated on Blackout (&lt;a href=&#34;https://ameliarose.itch.io/blackout%29,an&#34;&gt;https://ameliarose.itch.io/blackout),an&lt;/a&gt; atmospheric puzzle game set in an arctic research facility. In addition to designing and implementing many of the puzzle mechanics in the game, Greg was charged with communicating specific design parameters to me as I designed our interactive music system. He is a tirelessly hard worker, excellent communicator, and brilliant designer with a broad spectrum of technical chops&amp;ndash;I would highly recommend him to anyone looking for a talented and team-focused designer.&amp;rdquo; &lt;code&gt;Cole Swany - Man Down Studio, Respawn Entertainment, Bit Reactor  &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wizard101</title>
      <link>https://gregmillerga.me/games/wizard101/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gregmillerga.me/games/wizard101/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;role--associate-product-designer&#34;&gt;Role : Associate Product Designer&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Game Info: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wizard101.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.wizard101.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publisher: Gamigo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developer: KingsIsle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-i-did&#34;&gt;What I did:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;2022 – Present Day&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Crown Shop&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped Plan and Create Sales and In-game Events to run throughout the year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created the config files that ran the Loyalty Store and Crown Shop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;


&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Content Creation&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Owned and led multiple mechanics in Wizard101. Including Pets, Monstrology, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked on various Items and Packs to sell for our In-Game Currency (Crowns).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped the PvE and PvP team create rewards to give players for completing tough content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hooked up Art and Animations, and worked with Art to fix visual bugs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;


&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Tools Programming&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created tools in C# and Python to speed up development time and automate bug-prone tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked with Design and Product to help identify needs on both teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;


&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Research and Development&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created tools in C# and Python to speed up development time and automate bug-prone tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked with Design and Product to help identify needs on both teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;


&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Misc Tasks&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did some light world building in our guild house and in PvE content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;role--associate-product-designer&#34;&gt;Role : Associate Product Designer&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Game Info: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wizard101.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.wizard101.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publisher: Gamigo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developer: KingsIsle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-i-did&#34;&gt;What I did:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;2022 – Present Day&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Crown Shop&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped Plan and Create Sales and In-game Events to run throughout the year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created the config files that ran the Loyalty Store and Crown Shop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;


&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Content Creation&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Owned and led multiple mechanics in Wizard101. Including Pets, Monstrology, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked on various Items and Packs to sell for our In-Game Currency (Crowns).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped the PvE and PvP team create rewards to give players for completing tough content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hooked up Art and Animations, and worked with Art to fix visual bugs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;


&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Tools Programming&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created tools in C# and Python to speed up development time and automate bug-prone tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked with Design and Product to help identify needs on both teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;


&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Research and Development&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created tools in C# and Python to speed up development time and automate bug-prone tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked with Design and Product to help identify needs on both teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;


&lt;details&gt;
  &lt;summary&gt;Misc Tasks&lt;/summary&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did some light world building in our guild house and in PvE content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
